Once upon a time, there was a young woman.
The young woman was to marry a groom chosen by her parents,
and not her sweetheart, whom she loved.
She knew that her groom loved her very much,
but did her sweetheart care for her even more than that?
The young woman wasn't certain.
In the end, after wavering between the two of them,
the young woman even became unsure which one of them she really loved.
How long have I been searching for a way to return Mewtwo to the story?
All this time, I just took to hand whatever book struck me.
So why do I choose only books whose endings are missing?
Why?
What meaning is there to books with missing endings?
I...
Found you.
Geez, Duck, can't you go one day without getting stuck with cleaning?
Of course she can't.
Sorry.
Seriously, Duck.
No way!
What?
No, Duck, you mustn't look!
This is a shock.
Definitely.
Why'd you...
Oh, ow!
No, don't, Duck.
You mustn't look right there.
See?
Fuck here.
He smiled!
That totally ruins his bad boy appeal!
We're here to become a full-fledged elite!
Who is she?
Defending the bitingly sarcastic, fantastic Fakir!
Huh?
An older woman lover, huh?
We can't say that for certain yet!
That's right, Duck!
You should harbor unreasonable hopes!
Mind the truths!
Definitely break me!
Ahh!
My...
Huh?
Hey!
Oh, hey, Fakir!
Um...
Are you a friend of Fakir's?
Calling her just a friend?
That's some confidence she's got there!
Oh!
It's like I can see Duck's crying face before me!
I can't sit any longer!
We were all just on our way to the ice cream shop, right?
Um, they were just here.
You're an interesting person.
My name's Retzel.
What's yours?
Uh, mine's Duck.
Well, Miss Duck, Fakir and I are heading over to his house right now.
Would you like to come along?
What?
Retzel.
Why not?
Right?
Uh...
I'm impressed you found where I was.
You can't hide anything from me, Fakir.
Well, there's still...
Fakir, welcome home.
Hmm?
It's been a long time.
Uh, Retzel!
May I come in?
Of course.
Who do you go well with, Zora?
It's a new lovey dovey, Zora!
Uh, is this your...
Last I saw you, Mewtwo and I just entered the Academy.
That's right.
I must admit, I was really lonely then.
Here you go.
Thanks!
It's all right.
Come here.
Let's go.
Oh, let's go.
It's all right. I'm something of an older sister to Fakir.
Really? I mean, no, I wasn't really saying...
She's been like a mother ever since my parents died and I was taken in by Karan.
Sister's not lovey-dovey, Zura?
Then is Retzel lovey-dovey was killed?
Now, now, Zura.
How flattering. We look that way. That certainly would be nice.
You shouldn't tease adults like that, you know.
You always treat me as a child.
You know, I'm at an age where marrying someone wouldn't be odd.
Well, at my age, all you youngsters look the same.
I still see you as Fakir and Muto's playmate.
That's right. Where's Muto?
Oh, yeah. He's at school now. His dancing consumes him.
Aren't you always with him, saying I'll protect you, Muto?
And I will. You're staying here, right?
Actually, I plan to stay at the watermill.
I'll walk you there, then.
Thank you. But I think I want to take a little walk with Miss Duck.
Huh?
I'm a tiny bit jealous.
Fakir with a girl as cute as you.
Oh, no. I'm not cute at all.
The truth is, I'm always fighting with Fakir.
Actually, sometimes I just can't stand him, and you know...
I wonder if it's thanks to you that Fakir changed so much.
Huh?
Say, is Fakir still writing stories?
Writing stories?
The stories that boy used to write now and again.
Sometimes they came true.
What?
The stories he wrote actually came true?
He loved to write stories from the time he was very small.
They were just silly little stories.
But sometimes part of them would come true.
However, after he came to Kharon's house, he just stopped writing altogether.
Miss Retzel?
I've said a little too much.
I wonder if Fakir will scold me.
To think Fakir wrote stories, and they came true.
If he can do that...
Maybe...
Miss Duck?
Oh, sorry. I just remembered something.
Um, it was fun talking to you.
Fakir has changed.
No.
The one who's changed the most...
is me.
Protect, huh?
How do I protect him?
Who do I fight?
You have to help me, Fakir.
My heart, it feels so...
The story no longer has need of you.
The fight has begun.
The story is moving.
Whether I'm here or not.
But all I have is a sword.
I'll protect Mewtwo with this sword.
There you are.
Hey, Fakir, guess what Retzel told me.
She said stories you write have the power to come true.
She what?
If you really have that power,
and you write a story where Mewtwo gets saved in the end...
Fakir?
What are you saying?
Huh?
I said I heard some of the stories you wrote when you were little came true.
So...
Be quiet.
But Mewtwo could...
Shut up!
What do you mean?
Why are you talking to me that way?
Hey!
If I really could help Mewtwo by myself, Fakir,
I wouldn't be asking you.
But right now, I can't do anything.
I said be quiet.
I'll protect Mewtwo as a knight, end of story.
I won't take orders from you.
Fakir, why?
Hey, listen to me!
Fakir, come on, Fakir.
If you can help Mewtwo, then why won't you?
What's with you two?
We were waiting so we'd be ready when you came home crying.
So, what happened with the wonderful Fakir?
I don't care what happened to him.
Good, good.
Get mad and cry as much as you want.
And I thought we'd be able to help Mewtwo soon.
Why?
He's kind of scared.
I'm getting shivers down my spine.
Retzel.
Mewtwo, I'm jealous of you.
Of me?
If I could live unchanging like you.
That's not how it is.
See, I'm different than I was before.
I've gotten my heart back.
And that means now I can even accept your love for me.
Now that's some happy news.
Maybe I'll call off the wedding then.
Wedding?
That's Mr. Mewtwo, which means the girl is Miss Rue.
The two of them are getting married?
Is that right?
Getting married?
Students of mine getting married before my eyes?
There is no happier, more joyful thing for a teacher than marriage!
Congratulations.
Oh, thank you.
You don't look very happy.
Could it be you're wavering?
Of course not.
I was only joking before.
Hans loves me deeply from the bottom of his heart.
With him, I'm sure I can have a happy life.
Come now.
You can't lie to your own feelings, Ratzel.
You've got a pure and beautiful heart, haven't you?
I'm going now, Mewtwo.
I will have you love me and me alone.
Sacrifice your life and love me.
If I do what Father says, someday he'll be my prince alone.
Right, Father?
The fight between the prince and the raven is being fought with fiercer and fiercer desperation.
In a place where no one can see.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
She's totally toying with him.
That's right.
A Fakir played thoroughly by an adult woman and then just tossed away like yesterday's newspaper.
How wonderful.
Fakir said he would protect Mewtwo, so why?
I'll protect Mewtwo as a knight, end of story.
I won't take orders from you.
And it was starting to look like we'd be able to work together, too.
I don't like this.
No way I'll let it stay like this.
Hey, wait!
Where are you going, Doug, for the second round, huh?
That Doug really does love battles, doesn't she?
I see.
So Fakir said that.
I want to help someone.
And he's someone important to Fakir, too.
So I thought if Fakir wrote a story, maybe we could help this person.
But it looks like...
I'm sorry.
This is because I've said something I shouldn't have.
Huh?
Miss Doug, please.
Will you pretend that you never heard what I told you before?
But saving this guy will make Fakir happy, too.
In exchange, Fakir will end up hurt as well, though.
What?
A long time ago, a lot of crows once showed up in Goldcrowned Town.
Crows?
The crows attacked the townspeople indiscriminately.
Fakir was a child, but he must have wanted to do something to help.
He wrote a story where he became a hero and defeated the crows.
And then, just like Fakir had written, the crows came and attacked him.
But the ending was different than his story.
Afterwards, he got so he never talked about it,
as if he'd sealed those memories away.
He stopped writing stories, too.
I never knew Fakir had something like that happen to him.
It must still cut him deeply, and yet I...
Miss Doug, please.
Give Fakir some space.
What in the world am I doing?
I came to get you, Ratzel.
My beautiful bride.
Doc, what's wrong, Zora?
I'm the worst.
What should I say to Fakir?
You want to say something to Fakir, Zora?
Wow!
Lots of crows, Zora!
Oh, the water mill.
Could Mewtwo be trying to get Ratzel's...
Ratzel, I'll give you a love with no wavering.
You'll love only me, won't you?
Yes.
Yuto.
My Ratzel.
Come here and give your beautiful heart to me.
I am Yuto's bride.
Wait!
Who are you?
I am known as Princess Tutu.
Please come and dance with me, won't you, Miss Ratzel?
Princess Tutu...
If you really have that power and you write a story where Mewtwo gets saved in the end...
What is this awful feeling?
The power to make stories come true?
A power like that in me?
That's ridiculous.
Is it Mewtwo that Miss Ratzel is lovey-dovey with Zora?
That's a lovely wedding dress.
You have someone you're engaged to, right?
Then why are you...
Kara knows how I feel, but when I saw him, he said nothing.
He did nothing.
Hans, however, he assures me of his love for me.
He looks only at me and holds me close.
And I love him dearly as well.
Yet no matter what I do, I see Karan's face in my mind.
You're suffering because you're wavering between two loves.
Love only me and your wavering will vanish.
You mustn't go there.
Does wavering scare you?
It's something you feel because you truly love people.
What scares me is that I may still love Kara.
When that thought crosses my mind, being with him is...
It's painful.
Karan?
I don't want to waver.
Ratzel.
That's right.
If you love only me...
If I but love only Mewtwo.
No!
You're making a grave mistake, Miss Ratzel!
Just forget everything else!
And love only me!
Both of these things reflect your true heart, Miss Ratzel.
But is what you are grasping at right now your true feelings?
True and false have nothing to do with it.
People just love others because they want to be loved.
She wavers because she wonders which one will love her more.
Pain is how you truly feel.
So wake up!
You want to be happy with the one you love most, don't you?
I kept on weighing their loves against each other for the sake of my own happiness.
To escape the aching pain of my wavering,
I set out to get Fakir to write a story about me.
Even though I knew it would hurt him.
I'm a horrible woman.
To want to be loved by those we love is not an evil feeling.
I'm sure it hurts to waver between two loves.
But simply running away won't help you to escape that pain.
No! You! You should be loving only me!
Ratzel!
Mewtwo, I will not allow you to harm Ratzel.
How interesting.
Stop! The two of you fighting!
It's not going to...
Mewtwo, do you feel nothing?
You would even use Ratzel?
I was merely trying to save her!
Look here!
Trying to save her?
Don't sugarcoat me.
What, like you've done with your service?
Nights who can't even die shouldn't point fingers.
Pathetic.
How long will you go on shaming yourself?
Wielding that blessed sword of yours?
Mewtwo, stop it!
You know you can't lay a finger on me for Kier.
This sword isn't for slaying you with, Mewtwo.
Now wake up!
Remember your true self, Mewtwo.
Mewtwo.
Stop it.
Don't hurt Fakir.
Shut up.
Shut up!
Fakir!
Stop it.
Don't hurt Fakir.
You hear me, Raven?
Stop this.
Mewtwo?
Run!
Don't!
Don't come near me.
Mewtwo?
Retzel.
Fakir, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I was thinking only of myself.
All I wanted was to escape my pain, and I did something to hurt you.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I've already forgiven you, Retzel.
Even though Miss Retzel was suffering so much, she told me.
She told me that I ought to give you some space, and that's the truth.
It wasn't in Miss Retzel's heart to hurt you, Fakir.
Fakir.
It wasn't in Miss Retzel's heart to hurt you.
Don't hurt Fakir.
You hear me, Raven?
Stop this.
If I really could help Mewtwo by myself, Fakir, I wouldn't be asking you.
But right now, I can't do anything.
What can I do?
That's right.
You can write a letter to the president.
Fakir?
But wait, you're...
...
Retzel.
Retzel!
Oh, good morning.
What's that in your hand?
Did you write a story for me?
Karon, I wanted to tell you.
Hans and I are going to get married.
Huh?
So I see.
Congratulations.
Retzel...
You see, I realized what I wanted was to say a proper goodbye to Karon.
But I'll take this.
Thanks so much.
Your story didn't come true, huh?
No, it didn't.
Hmm.
I think I will try writing one.
What?
You know, a story about Muto.
That's dangerous.
That power is truly dangerous, you know.
Can someone like you, who couldn't attain mere knighthood, really master such a potent craft?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
They took out the endings to stop them from becoming real?
He's awakened.
This is dangerous.
It seems he's gained the knowledge, but that's all.
A direct descendant of Drosselmeyer's, and this is your level?
That hurts.
You hesitated to take my hand.
Muto was always kind to Rue, but...
To those who accept everything, happiness.
To those who resist everything, glory.
Bakir, please, you must wake up.
Oh, you children who love stories, come gather round.
Thank you.